{
    "music": [
      {
        "question": "Who had a 1969 top 5 hit with the song, 'A Boy Named Sue'?",
        "answers": ["Bob Dylan","Johnny Cash", "Willie Nelson", "Kris Kristofferson"],
        "correct_answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the album released in 2014 by American band Maroon 5?",
        "answers": ["X", "V", "III", "IV"],
        "correct_answer": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of singer Frank Ocean's second studio album, which was released on August 20, 2016?",
        "answers": ["Brunette", "Black", "Blonde", "Burgundy"],
        "correct_answer": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "How many strings are there on a cello?",
        "answers": [ "4","5", "6", "8"],
        "correct_answer": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "\"Hallelujah\" is a song written by which Canadian recording artist?",
        "answers": ["Kory Lefkowits", "Ryan Letourneau","Leonard Cohen", "Justin Bieber"],
        "correct_answer": 2
      }
    ],
    "Video Games": [
        {
            "question": "Which Game Boy from the Game Boy series of portable video game consoles was released first?",
            "answers": [
                "Game Boy Advance",
                "Game Boy Micro",
                "Game Boy Color",
                "Game Boy Advance SP"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the first weapon you acquire in Half-Life?",
            "answers": [
                "A crowbar",
                "A pistol",
                "The H.E.V suit",
                "Your fists"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these is not a wonder weapon in &quot;Call Of Duty: Zombies&quot;?",
            "answers": [
                "GKZ-45 Mk3",
                "Ray Gun",
                "Scavenger",
                "R115 Resonator"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "In which year was League of Legends released?",
            "answers": [
                "2010",
                "2009",
                "2003",
                "2001"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the adventurer you meet at the mines in Stardew Valley?",
            "answers": [
                "Marnie",
                "Marvin",
                "Morris",
                "Marlon"
            ],
            "correct_answer": 3
        }
    ]
  }
  
      